{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681011636","data":{"timestamp":" 947681011635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 4186049c-77ac-4533-9bd1-7151496b52b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" la"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681012681","data":{"timestamp":" 947681012680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 4186049c-77ac-4533-9bd1-7151496b52b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" la"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681015703","data":{"timestamp":" 947681015702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 4186049c-77ac-4533-9bd1-7151496b52b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" le"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LE"," userResponse":" LE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681016774","data":{"timestamp":" 947681016774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 4186049c-77ac-4533-9bd1-7151496b52b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" le"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LE"," userResponse":" LE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681025546","data":{"timestamp":" 947681025546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 4186049c-77ac-4533-9bd1-7151496b52b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" li"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681026622","data":{"timestamp":" 947681026621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 4186049c-77ac-4533-9bd1-7151496b52b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" li"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LI"," userResponse":" LI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681030878","data":{"timestamp":" 947681030877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 4186049c-77ac-4533-9bd1-7151496b52b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681031929","data":{"timestamp":" 947681031929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 4186049c-77ac-4533-9bd1-7151496b52b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LO"," userResponse":" LO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681036858","data":{"timestamp":" 947681036858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 4186049c-77ac-4533-9bd1-7151496b52b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681037912","data":{"timestamp":" 947681037912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 4186049c-77ac-4533-9bd1-7151496b52b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LU"," userResponse":" LU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681041158","data":{"timestamp":" 947681041156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 4186049c-77ac-4533-9bd1-7151496b52b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" lu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681041307","data":{"timestamp":" 947681041307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 4186049c-77ac-4533-9bd1-7151496b52b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LU"," userResponse":" LU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..102.off10.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681164403","data":{"timestamp":" 947681164398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 4186049c-77ac-4533-9bd1-7151496b52b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" lu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681179054","data":{"timestamp":" 947681179054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 35fc424e-c02e-4030-9130-d0205154dfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681184697","data":{"timestamp":" 947681184697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 35fc424e-c02e-4030-9130-d0205154dfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681197596","data":{"timestamp":" 947681197596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 35fc424e-c02e-4030-9130-d0205154dfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681207548","data":{"timestamp":" 947681207548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 35fc424e-c02e-4030-9130-d0205154dfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681220625","data":{"timestamp":" 947681220625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 35fc424e-c02e-4030-9130-d0205154dfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681227921","data":{"timestamp":" 947681227921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 35fc424e-c02e-4030-9130-d0205154dfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681264821","data":{"timestamp":" 947681264821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 35fc424e-c02e-4030-9130-d0205154dfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681275318","data":{"timestamp":" 947681275317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 35fc424e-c02e-4030-9130-d0205154dfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681293129","data":{"timestamp":" 947681293128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 35fc424e-c02e-4030-9130-d0205154dfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681306364","data":{"timestamp":" 947681306364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 35fc424e-c02e-4030-9130-d0205154dfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681312132","data":{"timestamp":" 947681312130"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 35fc424e-c02e-4030-9130-d0205154dfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681330931","data":{"timestamp":" 947681330930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 23ac5a8f-e6c0-4e32-9f3c-09807eb4fe51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681331153","data":{"timestamp":" 947681331152"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 23ac5a8f-e6c0-4e32-9f3c-09807eb4fe51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681332116","data":{"timestamp":" 947681332116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 23ac5a8f-e6c0-4e32-9f3c-09807eb4fe51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681333390","data":{"timestamp":" 947681333389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 23ac5a8f-e6c0-4e32-9f3c-09807eb4fe51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681336226","data":{"timestamp":" 947681336225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 23ac5a8f-e6c0-4e32-9f3c-09807eb4fe51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681337068","data":{"timestamp":" 947681337068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 23ac5a8f-e6c0-4e32-9f3c-09807eb4fe51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681337381","data":{"timestamp":" 947681337381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 23ac5a8f-e6c0-4e32-9f3c-09807eb4fe51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681338614","data":{"timestamp":" 947681338614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 23ac5a8f-e6c0-4e32-9f3c-09807eb4fe51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681342093","data":{"timestamp":" 947681342093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 23ac5a8f-e6c0-4e32-9f3c-09807eb4fe51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681343090","data":{"timestamp":" 947681343089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 23ac5a8f-e6c0-4e32-9f3c-09807eb4fe51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681343353","data":{"timestamp":" 947681343352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 23ac5a8f-e6c0-4e32-9f3c-09807eb4fe51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681344243","data":{"timestamp":" 947681344243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 23ac5a8f-e6c0-4e32-9f3c-09807eb4fe51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681344332","data":{"timestamp":" 947681344332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 23ac5a8f-e6c0-4e32-9f3c-09807eb4fe51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681355784","data":{"timestamp":" 947681355783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681356006","data":{"timestamp":" 947681356006"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681356977","data":{"timestamp":" 947681356976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681358262","data":{"timestamp":" 947681358262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681361147","data":{"timestamp":" 947681361147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681361990","data":{"timestamp":" 947681361990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681362302","data":{"timestamp":" 947681362302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681363535","data":{"timestamp":" 947681363535"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681367096","data":{"timestamp":" 947681367095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681368092","data":{"timestamp":" 947681368091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681368354","data":{"timestamp":" 947681368353"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681369312","data":{"timestamp":" 947681369312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681372202","data":{"timestamp":" 947681372202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681373240","data":{"timestamp":" 947681373240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681373723","data":{"timestamp":" 947681373721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681378330","data":{"timestamp":" 947681378328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681378454","data":{"timestamp":" 947681378454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 3e31f1cf-1d8f-4106-baeb-33cd7f9baaa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681409733","data":{"timestamp":" 947681409733"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" ae51a952-e48a-4779-b4e0-0679dab61094"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_da-mwi-kwi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681415304","data":{"timestamp":" 947681415304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" ae51a952-e48a-4779-b4e0-0679dab61094"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_va-mcho-da"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681588921","data":{"timestamp":" 947681588920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" ae51a952-e48a-4779-b4e0-0679dab61094"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_msta-da-mlo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" mlo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681599945","data":{"timestamp":" 947681599945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" ae51a952-e48a-4779-b4e0-0679dab61094"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_msta-da-mlo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681621157","data":{"timestamp":" 947681621157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" ae51a952-e48a-4779-b4e0-0679dab61094"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_da-ma-kwe"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681634328","data":{"timestamp":" 947681634328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" ae51a952-e48a-4779-b4e0-0679dab61094"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_sa-mti-da"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681645710","data":{"timestamp":" 947681645710"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" ae51a952-e48a-4779-b4e0-0679dab61094"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_nji-da-ru"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681654575","data":{"timestamp":" 947681654575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" ae51a952-e48a-4779-b4e0-0679dab61094"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_da-kha-vo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681674518","data":{"timestamp":" 947681674518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" ae51a952-e48a-4779-b4e0-0679dab61094"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_vya-da-chi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681679940","data":{"timestamp":" 947681679940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" ae51a952-e48a-4779-b4e0-0679dab61094"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_mka-da-mwe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681685872","data":{"timestamp":" 947681685872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" ae51a952-e48a-4779-b4e0-0679dab61094"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_zo-ze-da"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681691626","data":{"timestamp":" 947681691625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" ae51a952-e48a-4779-b4e0-0679dab61094"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_da_zo-ze-da"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..102.off10.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681752304","data":{"timestamp":" 947681752303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" ae51a952-e48a-4779-b4e0-0679dab61094"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.show.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_da_zo-ze-da"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681763564","data":{"timestamp":" 947681763564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 39682223-58ec-43a5-894a-8887d68d419a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" da"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DA"," userResponse":" DA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681767169","data":{"timestamp":" 947681767169"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 39682223-58ec-43a5-894a-8887d68d419a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" da"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681768757","data":{"timestamp":" 947681768757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 39682223-58ec-43a5-894a-8887d68d419a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" de"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DE"," userResponse":" DE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681771278","data":{"timestamp":" 947681771277"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 39682223-58ec-43a5-894a-8887d68d419a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" de"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DE"," userResponse":" DE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681772890","data":{"timestamp":" 947681772890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 39682223-58ec-43a5-894a-8887d68d419a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" di"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DI"," userResponse":" DI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681779294","data":{"timestamp":" 947681779293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 39682223-58ec-43a5-894a-8887d68d419a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" di"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DI"," userResponse":" DI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681780883","data":{"timestamp":" 947681780883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 39682223-58ec-43a5-894a-8887d68d419a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" do"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DO"," userResponse":" DO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681784788","data":{"timestamp":" 947681784788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 39682223-58ec-43a5-894a-8887d68d419a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" do"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DO"," userResponse":" DO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681786408","data":{"timestamp":" 947681786408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 39682223-58ec-43a5-894a-8887d68d419a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" du"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DU"," userResponse":" DU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681790198","data":{"timestamp":" 947681790197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 39682223-58ec-43a5-894a-8887d68d419a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" du"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DU"," userResponse":" DU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.da..du.asc.lc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681792217","data":{"timestamp":" 947681792216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 39682223-58ec-43a5-894a-8887d68d419a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" du"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681792312","data":{"timestamp":" 947681792312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 39682223-58ec-43a5-894a-8887d68d419a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.da..du.asc.lc.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" du"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DU"," userResponse":" DU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681801755","data":{"timestamp":" 947681801754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681801978","data":{"timestamp":" 947681801978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681802953","data":{"timestamp":" 947681802952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681804239","data":{"timestamp":" 947681804239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681807218","data":{"timestamp":" 947681807217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681808071","data":{"timestamp":" 947681808070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681808392","data":{"timestamp":" 947681808391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681809638","data":{"timestamp":" 947681809638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681813188","data":{"timestamp":" 947681813187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681814183","data":{"timestamp":" 947681814182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681814453","data":{"timestamp":" 947681814453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681815422","data":{"timestamp":" 947681815421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681818287","data":{"timestamp":" 947681818286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681819328","data":{"timestamp":" 947681819328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681819809","data":{"timestamp":" 947681819808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681824395","data":{"timestamp":" 947681824395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681824465","data":{"timestamp":" 947681824464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 407293dd-a051-4462-b8ff-20ef7d4e2408"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681838072","data":{"timestamp":" 947681838072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 241c9e08-a5c8-46fb-a554-48d51f57f52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_twe-da-mwi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681843349","data":{"timestamp":" 947681843349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 241c9e08-a5c8-46fb-a554-48d51f57f52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_mgo-da-za"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681848576","data":{"timestamp":" 947681848575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 241c9e08-a5c8-46fb-a554-48d51f57f52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_ngi-da-nyi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681870771","data":{"timestamp":" 947681870771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 241c9e08-a5c8-46fb-a554-48d51f57f52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_ri-da-tha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681875023","data":{"timestamp":" 947681875022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 241c9e08-a5c8-46fb-a554-48d51f57f52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_da-mka-ve"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681880108","data":{"timestamp":" 947681880108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 241c9e08-a5c8-46fb-a554-48d51f57f52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_ju-yi-da"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681884876","data":{"timestamp":" 947681884876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 241c9e08-a5c8-46fb-a554-48d51f57f52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_mre-nya-da"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681889902","data":{"timestamp":" 947681889902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 241c9e08-a5c8-46fb-a554-48d51f57f52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_mu-ng'a-da"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681894688","data":{"timestamp":" 947681894687"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 241c9e08-a5c8-46fb-a554-48d51f57f52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_dha-nye-da"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681899832","data":{"timestamp":" 947681899831"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 241c9e08-a5c8-46fb-a554-48d51f57f52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_da_shu-da-vyu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681905588","data":{"timestamp":" 947681905587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 241c9e08-a5c8-46fb-a554-48d51f57f52e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_da..da.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_da_shu-da-vyu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681915970","data":{"timestamp":" 947681915969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 28bcbbd1-9d1c-4a40-9931-6294c8f9d0ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_26_2-26-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 26"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681922841","data":{"timestamp":" 947681922841"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 28bcbbd1-9d1c-4a40-9931-6294c8f9d0ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_26_2-26-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 26"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681929068","data":{"timestamp":" 947681929068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 28bcbbd1-9d1c-4a40-9931-6294c8f9d0ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_26_2-26-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 26"," userResponse":" 26"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681939418","data":{"timestamp":" 947681939418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 28bcbbd1-9d1c-4a40-9931-6294c8f9d0ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_27_27-6-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 27"," userResponse":" 27"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681948573","data":{"timestamp":" 947681948573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 28bcbbd1-9d1c-4a40-9931-6294c8f9d0ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_23_11-7-23"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 23"," userResponse":" 23"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681956852","data":{"timestamp":" 947681956852"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 28bcbbd1-9d1c-4a40-9931-6294c8f9d0ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_21_5-3-21"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 21"," userResponse":" 21"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681965557","data":{"timestamp":" 947681965557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 28bcbbd1-9d1c-4a40-9931-6294c8f9d0ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_25_25-10-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 25"," userResponse":" 25"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681973494","data":{"timestamp":" 947681973494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 28bcbbd1-9d1c-4a40-9931-6294c8f9d0ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_25_25-10-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 25"," userResponse":" 25"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681980944","data":{"timestamp":" 947681980944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 28bcbbd1-9d1c-4a40-9931-6294c8f9d0ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_23_11-4-23"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 23"," userResponse":" 23"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681990644","data":{"timestamp":" 947681990644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 28bcbbd1-9d1c-4a40-9931-6294c8f9d0ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_25_8-25-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 25"," userResponse":" 25"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947681996800","data":{"timestamp":" 947681996800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 28bcbbd1-9d1c-4a40-9931-6294c8f9d0ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_23_9-10-23"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 23"," userResponse":" 23"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682002966","data":{"timestamp":" 947682002966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 28bcbbd1-9d1c-4a40-9931-6294c8f9d0ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_29_1-10-29"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 29"," userResponse":" 29"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682010519","data":{"timestamp":" 947682010518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 28bcbbd1-9d1c-4a40-9931-6294c8f9d0ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL3.incr.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_29_1-10-29"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682020435","data":{"timestamp":" 947682020435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f8cc8180-b0db-452c-ae0a-0d6b9da2cea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682026097","data":{"timestamp":" 947682026097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f8cc8180-b0db-452c-ae0a-0d6b9da2cea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682047502","data":{"timestamp":" 947682047501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f8cc8180-b0db-452c-ae0a-0d6b9da2cea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682066910","data":{"timestamp":" 947682066910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f8cc8180-b0db-452c-ae0a-0d6b9da2cea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682077642","data":{"timestamp":" 947682077642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f8cc8180-b0db-452c-ae0a-0d6b9da2cea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682080863","data":{"timestamp":" 947682080863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f8cc8180-b0db-452c-ae0a-0d6b9da2cea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682090148","data":{"timestamp":" 947682090148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682090371","data":{"timestamp":" 947682090371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682091339","data":{"timestamp":" 947682091338"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682092612","data":{"timestamp":" 947682092612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682095573","data":{"timestamp":" 947682095573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682096432","data":{"timestamp":" 947682096431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682096759","data":{"timestamp":" 947682096758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682098021","data":{"timestamp":" 947682098021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682101543","data":{"timestamp":" 947682101543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682102547","data":{"timestamp":" 947682102547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682102813","data":{"timestamp":" 947682102812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682103768","data":{"timestamp":" 947682103768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682106668","data":{"timestamp":" 947682106667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682107708","data":{"timestamp":" 947682107707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682108188","data":{"timestamp":" 947682108187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682112733","data":{"timestamp":" 947682112732"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682112802","data":{"timestamp":" 947682112802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 42ba63e4-8d21-45ad-92d7-a54b1681abf9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682120934","data":{"timestamp":" 947682120933"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682121316","data":{"timestamp":" 947682121316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682121548","data":{"timestamp":" 947682121548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682121870","data":{"timestamp":" 947682121870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682122110","data":{"timestamp":" 947682122110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682125587","data":{"timestamp":" 947682125587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682125894","data":{"timestamp":" 947682125893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682126806","data":{"timestamp":" 947682126805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682127245","data":{"timestamp":" 947682127245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682130201","data":{"timestamp":" 947682130196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682130497","data":{"timestamp":" 947682130496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682131354","data":{"timestamp":" 947682131354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682132030","data":{"timestamp":" 947682132029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682132772","data":{"timestamp":" 947682132772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682133104","data":{"timestamp":" 947682133103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682133391","data":{"timestamp":" 947682133391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682133713","data":{"timestamp":" 947682133713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682133987","data":{"timestamp":" 947682133986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682137676","data":{"timestamp":" 947682137675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682138069","data":{"timestamp":" 947682138068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682138309","data":{"timestamp":" 947682138309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682138631","data":{"timestamp":" 947682138631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682138871","data":{"timestamp":" 947682138871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682142372","data":{"timestamp":" 947682142372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682142670","data":{"timestamp":" 947682142670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682143588","data":{"timestamp":" 947682143588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682144017","data":{"timestamp":" 947682144017"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682147001","data":{"timestamp":" 947682147001"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682147298","data":{"timestamp":" 947682147298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682148154","data":{"timestamp":" 947682148153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682148829","data":{"timestamp":" 947682148829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682149581","data":{"timestamp":" 947682149581"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682149914","data":{"timestamp":" 947682149914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682150206","data":{"timestamp":" 947682150204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682150519","data":{"timestamp":" 947682150519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682150791","data":{"timestamp":" 947682150791"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682154263","data":{"timestamp":" 947682154263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682154323","data":{"timestamp":" 947682154323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 0524b59e-f95c-44a9-9082-98449e40c77e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682177925","data":{"timestamp":" 947682177925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" df198c23-6253-466a-b02c-0b7b5b4af731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_9-12-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682189543","data":{"timestamp":" 947682189543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" df198c23-6253-466a-b02c-0b7b5b4af731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_9-12-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682196622","data":{"timestamp":" 947682196622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" df198c23-6253-466a-b02c-0b7b5b4af731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_14_4-13-14"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 14"," userResponse":" 14"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682203962","data":{"timestamp":" 947682203961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" df198c23-6253-466a-b02c-0b7b5b4af731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_19_8-19-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 19"," userResponse":" 19"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682209729","data":{"timestamp":" 947682209729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" df198c23-6253-466a-b02c-0b7b5b4af731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_9-10-12"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682214807","data":{"timestamp":" 947682214807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" df198c23-6253-466a-b02c-0b7b5b4af731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-10-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682221090","data":{"timestamp":" 947682221089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" df198c23-6253-466a-b02c-0b7b5b4af731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-10-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682227959","data":{"timestamp":" 947682227959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" df198c23-6253-466a-b02c-0b7b5b4af731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_7-5-15"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682234790","data":{"timestamp":" 947682234790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" df198c23-6253-466a-b02c-0b7b5b4af731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_19_2-19-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 19"," userResponse":" 19"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682242352","data":{"timestamp":" 947682242352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" df198c23-6253-466a-b02c-0b7b5b4af731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_14_0-14-7"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 14"," userResponse":" 14"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682248464","data":{"timestamp":" 947682248463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" df198c23-6253-466a-b02c-0b7b5b4af731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_13_4-12-13"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 13"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682255451","data":{"timestamp":" 947682255451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" df198c23-6253-466a-b02c-0b7b5b4af731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-12-13"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682262546","data":{"timestamp":" 947682262544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" df198c23-6253-466a-b02c-0b7b5b4af731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL2.incr.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-12-13"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682283033","data":{"timestamp":" 947682283032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f52b917c-f4a7-4b2d-91ff-3f9cdfbfb604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mfu_mlu_ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682289654","data":{"timestamp":" 947682289654"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f52b917c-f4a7-4b2d-91ff-3f9cdfbfb604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_mwu_mu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682296311","data":{"timestamp":" 947682296311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f52b917c-f4a7-4b2d-91ff-3f9cdfbfb604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_mpe_bi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682302969","data":{"timestamp":" 947682302969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f52b917c-f4a7-4b2d-91ff-3f9cdfbfb604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_ko_la"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682309607","data":{"timestamp":" 947682309607"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f52b917c-f4a7-4b2d-91ff-3f9cdfbfb604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_mvu_ndi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682316214","data":{"timestamp":" 947682316213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f52b917c-f4a7-4b2d-91ff-3f9cdfbfb604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_cha_mko"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682322822","data":{"timestamp":" 947682322822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f52b917c-f4a7-4b2d-91ff-3f9cdfbfb604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_swa_si_ni"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682329455","data":{"timestamp":" 947682329454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f52b917c-f4a7-4b2d-91ff-3f9cdfbfb604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_nja_we"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682336919","data":{"timestamp":" 947682336919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f52b917c-f4a7-4b2d-91ff-3f9cdfbfb604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_nja_we"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682343558","data":{"timestamp":" 947682343558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f52b917c-f4a7-4b2d-91ff-3f9cdfbfb604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_mtu_mbi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682350186","data":{"timestamp":" 947682350185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f52b917c-f4a7-4b2d-91ff-3f9cdfbfb604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_mpa_ya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682357624","data":{"timestamp":" 947682357624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f52b917c-f4a7-4b2d-91ff-3f9cdfbfb604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ni_mpa_ya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682370753","data":{"timestamp":" 947682370752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" f52b917c-f4a7-4b2d-91ff-3f9cdfbfb604"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ni..ni.noShow..12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_ni_mpa_ya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682380267","data":{"timestamp":" 947682380267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682380507","data":{"timestamp":" 947682380506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682381486","data":{"timestamp":" 947682381486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682382772","data":{"timestamp":" 947682382771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682385656","data":{"timestamp":" 947682385656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682386516","data":{"timestamp":" 947682386515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682386872","data":{"timestamp":" 947682386872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682388118","data":{"timestamp":" 947682388117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682391690","data":{"timestamp":" 947682391689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682392687","data":{"timestamp":" 947682392686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682392947","data":{"timestamp":" 947682392946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682393901","data":{"timestamp":" 947682393901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682396849","data":{"timestamp":" 947682396848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682397896","data":{"timestamp":" 947682397895"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682398382","data":{"timestamp":" 947682398381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682402973","data":{"timestamp":" 947682402972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682403070","data":{"timestamp":" 947682403070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" c4c65844-deb5-4eef-8535-5047704b6fda"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682413967","data":{"timestamp":" 947682413966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 311b931a-e66c-45dc-a13b-937a1172015d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682418531","data":{"timestamp":" 947682418530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 311b931a-e66c-45dc-a13b-937a1172015d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682420144","data":{"timestamp":" 947682420143"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 311b931a-e66c-45dc-a13b-937a1172015d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NE"," userResponse":" NE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682424113","data":{"timestamp":" 947682424112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 311b931a-e66c-45dc-a13b-937a1172015d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NE"," userResponse":" NE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682425706","data":{"timestamp":" 947682425706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 311b931a-e66c-45dc-a13b-937a1172015d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682427973","data":{"timestamp":" 947682427972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 311b931a-e66c-45dc-a13b-937a1172015d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682429558","data":{"timestamp":" 947682429558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 311b931a-e66c-45dc-a13b-937a1172015d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" no"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NO"," userResponse":" NO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682433142","data":{"timestamp":" 947682433141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 311b931a-e66c-45dc-a13b-937a1172015d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" no"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682434730","data":{"timestamp":" 947682434730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 311b931a-e66c-45dc-a13b-937a1172015d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NU"," userResponse":" NU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682438239","data":{"timestamp":" 947682438239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 311b931a-e66c-45dc-a13b-937a1172015d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682440246","data":{"timestamp":" 947682440246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 311b931a-e66c-45dc-a13b-937a1172015d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682440420","data":{"timestamp":" 947682440419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 311b931a-e66c-45dc-a13b-937a1172015d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.na..nu.asc.lc.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682457533","data":{"timestamp":" 947682457533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682466545","data":{"timestamp":" 947682466545"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-5-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682475741","data":{"timestamp":" 947682475741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-2-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682483869","data":{"timestamp":" 947682483869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-12-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682490712","data":{"timestamp":" 947682490712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-12-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682501118","data":{"timestamp":" 947682501118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_2-5-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682507787","data":{"timestamp":" 947682507787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_2-5-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682512514","data":{"timestamp":" 947682512514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_10-2-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682517175","data":{"timestamp":" 947682517175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_11-1-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682521342","data":{"timestamp":" 947682521342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-11-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682526311","data":{"timestamp":" 947682526310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-3-1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682532397","data":{"timestamp":" 947682532397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-3-1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682537132","data":{"timestamp":" 947682537132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_0-9-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682543696","data":{"timestamp":" 947682543696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_3_0-9-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.na..nu.asc.lc.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682554038","data":{"timestamp":" 947682554037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 61609359-38d8-417e-a7e9-0f7b244929e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_0-9-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682566436","data":{"timestamp":" 947682566435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682566667","data":{"timestamp":" 947682566667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682567645","data":{"timestamp":" 947682567644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682568926","data":{"timestamp":" 947682568926"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682571900","data":{"timestamp":" 947682571899"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682572759","data":{"timestamp":" 947682572758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682573079","data":{"timestamp":" 947682573079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682574332","data":{"timestamp":" 947682574331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682577877","data":{"timestamp":" 947682577876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682578869","data":{"timestamp":" 947682578868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682579132","data":{"timestamp":" 947682579132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682580088","data":{"timestamp":" 947682580087"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682583021","data":{"timestamp":" 947682583020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682584066","data":{"timestamp":" 947682584066"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682584545","data":{"timestamp":" 947682584544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682589150","data":{"timestamp":" 947682589148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682589253","data":{"timestamp":" 947682589253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 249151bc-e716-4693-8d0a-4280a85c5731"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682598872","data":{"timestamp":" 947682598872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 857b516c-9af2-45cf-820f-0ac1c594bc3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682605673","data":{"timestamp":" 947682605673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 857b516c-9af2-45cf-820f-0ac1c594bc3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682613201","data":{"timestamp":" 947682613201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 857b516c-9af2-45cf-820f-0ac1c594bc3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682619451","data":{"timestamp":" 947682619451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 857b516c-9af2-45cf-820f-0ac1c594bc3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682626838","data":{"timestamp":" 947682626838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 857b516c-9af2-45cf-820f-0ac1c594bc3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682631575","data":{"timestamp":" 947682631575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 857b516c-9af2-45cf-820f-0ac1c594bc3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682637164","data":{"timestamp":" 947682637163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 857b516c-9af2-45cf-820f-0ac1c594bc3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682641952","data":{"timestamp":" 947682641952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 857b516c-9af2-45cf-820f-0ac1c594bc3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682669120","data":{"timestamp":" 947682669120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 857b516c-9af2-45cf-820f-0ac1c594bc3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682676313","data":{"timestamp":" 947682676312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 857b516c-9af2-45cf-820f-0ac1c594bc3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682685643","data":{"timestamp":" 947682685642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 857b516c-9af2-45cf-820f-0ac1c594bc3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682696563","data":{"timestamp":" 947682696563"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682696948","data":{"timestamp":" 947682696947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682697180","data":{"timestamp":" 947682697180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682697492","data":{"timestamp":" 947682697492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682697725","data":{"timestamp":" 947682697725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682701147","data":{"timestamp":" 947682701147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682701440","data":{"timestamp":" 947682701440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682702344","data":{"timestamp":" 947682702344"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682702768","data":{"timestamp":" 947682702767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682705642","data":{"timestamp":" 947682705642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682705925","data":{"timestamp":" 947682705925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682706769","data":{"timestamp":" 947682706769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682707432","data":{"timestamp":" 947682707432"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682708166","data":{"timestamp":" 947682708166"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682708489","data":{"timestamp":" 947682708489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682708763","data":{"timestamp":" 947682708763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682709077","data":{"timestamp":" 947682709077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682709341","data":{"timestamp":" 947682709340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682709571","data":{"timestamp":" 947682709570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682709655","data":{"timestamp":" 947682709655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 04c30cc7-7769-4b4e-b66f-573ba56e2314"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682719453","data":{"timestamp":" 947682719453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682719684","data":{"timestamp":" 947682719684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682720647","data":{"timestamp":" 947682720647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682721920","data":{"timestamp":" 947682721920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682724846","data":{"timestamp":" 947682724846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682725689","data":{"timestamp":" 947682725689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682726002","data":{"timestamp":" 947682726002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682727235","data":{"timestamp":" 947682727235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682730783","data":{"timestamp":" 947682730782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682731778","data":{"timestamp":" 947682731777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682732039","data":{"timestamp":" 947682732038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682732995","data":{"timestamp":" 947682732994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682735950","data":{"timestamp":" 947682735949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682736996","data":{"timestamp":" 947682736995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682737473","data":{"timestamp":" 947682737473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682742089","data":{"timestamp":" 947682742089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947682742176","data":{"timestamp":" 947682742176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154313"," gameId":" 58a7a469-b068-422a-98b3-e5e6302c1b29"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}